{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, H, L, Q and directed edges M->H, H->L, H->Q, L->Q, M->L, M->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "87202888", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from L to H.", "answer": "['L<-H', 'L->Q<-H', 'L<-M->H', 'L->Q<-M->H', 'L<-M->Q<-H']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, H, L, Q and directed edges M->H, H->L, H->Q, L->Q, M->L, M->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "87202888", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from L to Q.", "answer": "5", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, H, L, Q and directed edges M->H, H->L, H->Q, L->Q, M->L, M->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "87202888", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from M to L.", "answer": ["M->L", "M->Q<-L", "M->H->L", "M->Q<-H->L", "M->H->Q<-L"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, H, L, Q and directed edges M->H, H->L, H->Q, L->Q, M->L, M->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "87202888", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from M to L.", "answer": "M->L", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, H, L, Q and directed edges M->H, H->L, H->Q, L->Q, M->L, M->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "87202888", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from M to L.", "answer": "M->Q<-H->L", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, H, L, Q and directed edges M->H, H->L, H->Q, L->Q, M->L, M->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "87202888", "sid": 5, "question": "Is H<-M a path from H to M?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, H, L, Q and directed edges M->H, H->L, H->Q, L->Q, M->L, M->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "87202888", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from H to Q?\nA. H<-L->Q\nB. H<->L<-M->Q\nC. H<-M<-L<->Q\nD. H->L<-M->Q", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, M, B, D and directed edges K->M, K->B, B->D, M->B, M->D, K->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "30190816", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from M to B.", "answer": "['M->B', 'M<-K->B', 'M->D<-B', 'M<-K->D<-B', 'M->D<-K->B']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, M, B, D and directed edges K->M, K->B, B->D, M->B, M->D, K->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "30190816", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from B to M.", "answer": "5", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, M, B, D and directed edges K->M, K->B, B->D, M->B, M->D, K->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "30190816", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from K to B.", "answer": ["K->B", "K->M->B", "K->D<-B", "K->M->D<-B", "K->D<-M->B"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, M, B, D and directed edges K->M, K->B, B->D, M->B, M->D, K->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "30190816", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from K to B.", "answer": "K->B", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, M, B, D and directed edges K->M, K->B, B->D, M->B, M->D, K->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "30190816", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from K to B.", "answer": "K->M->D<-B", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, M, B, D and directed edges K->M, K->B, B->D, M->B, M->D, K->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "30190816", "sid": 5, "question": "Is M<-D->K<-B a path from M to B?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, M, B, D and directed edges K->M, K->B, B->D, M->B, M->D, K->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "30190816", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from B to K?\nA. B<-M<-K\nB. B->D<-M<->K\nC. B<-M<-D->K\nD. B<-D->M->K", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, G, K, T, O and directed edges K->T, P->K, G->K, G->O, P->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22411272", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from T to P.", "answer": "['T<-K<-P', 'T<-K<-G<-P']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, G, K, T, O and directed edges K->T, P->K, G->K, G->O, P->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22411272", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from P to T.", "answer": "2", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, G, K, T, O and directed edges K->T, P->K, G->K, G->O, P->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22411272", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from P to G.", "answer": ["P->G", "P->K<-G"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, G, K, T, O and directed edges K->T, P->K, G->K, G->O, P->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22411272", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from P to G.", "answer": "P->G", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, G, K, T, O and directed edges K->T, P->K, G->K, G->O, P->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22411272", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from P to G.", "answer": "P->K<-G", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, G, K, T, O and directed edges K->T, P->K, G->K, G->O, P->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22411272", "sid": 5, "question": "Is T<-K a path from T to K?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, G, K, T, O and directed edges K->T, P->K, G->K, G->O, P->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22411272", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from K to O?\nA. K<-G->O\nB. K->G<->O\nC. K<-T<-G<-P<-O\nD. K->T->G<-P<->O", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes C, F, S, T, U and directed edges C->F, F->T, F->S, T->U, C->U, C->T, F->U.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "78311555", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from F to T.", "answer": "['F->T', 'F->U<-T', 'F<-C->T', 'F->U<-C->T', 'F<-C->U<-T']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes C, F, S, T, U and directed edges C->F, F->T, F->S, T->U, C->U, C->T, F->U.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "78311555", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from C to T.", "answer": "5", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes C, F, S, T, U and directed edges C->F, F->T, F->S, T->U, C->U, C->T, F->U.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "78311555", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from C to T.", "answer": ["C->T", "C->U<-T", "C->F->T", "C->U<-F->T", "C->F->U<-T"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes C, F, S, T, U and directed edges C->F, F->T, F->S, T->U, C->U, C->T, F->U.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "78311555", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from C to T.", "answer": "C->T", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes C, F, S, T, U and directed edges C->F, F->T, F->S, T->U, C->U, C->T, F->U.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "78311555", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from C to T.", "answer": "C->U<-F->T", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes C, F, S, T, U and directed edges C->F, F->T, F->S, T->U, C->U, C->T, F->U.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "78311555", "sid": 5, "question": "Is C<-U<->T<->F a path from C to F?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes C, F, S, T, U and directed edges C->F, F->T, F->S, T->U, C->U, C->T, F->U.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "78311555", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from C to F?\nA. C<->T->F\nB. C->T->U<-F\nC. C->U->F\nD. C->T->F", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, O, J, N, Q, H and directed edges N->Q, B->J, O->J, N->H, B->H, B->O.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "84174438", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from Q to H.", "answer": "['Q<-N->H']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, O, J, N, Q, H and directed edges N->Q, B->J, O->J, N->H, B->H, B->O.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "84174438", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from N to Q.", "answer": "1", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, O, J, N, Q, H and directed edges N->Q, B->J, O->J, N->H, B->H, B->O.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "84174438", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from O to H.", "answer": ["O<-B->H", "O->J<-B->H"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, O, J, N, Q, H and directed edges N->Q, B->J, O->J, N->H, B->H, B->O.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "84174438", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from O to H.", "answer": "O<-B->H", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, O, J, N, Q, H and directed edges N->Q, B->J, O->J, N->H, B->H, B->O.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "84174438", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from O to H.", "answer": "O->J<-B->H", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, O, J, N, Q, H and directed edges N->Q, B->J, O->J, N->H, B->H, B->O.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "84174438", "sid": 5, "question": "Is B->H<-N<-J<->Q a path from B to Q?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, O, J, N, Q, H and directed edges N->Q, B->J, O->J, N->H, B->H, B->O.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "84174438", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from Q to B?\nA. Q->O->B\nB. Q<-J<->N<->B\nC. Q<-N->H<-B\nD. Q->J<->O->N->B", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, H, N, T, P, Y and directed edges H->N, I->H, I->P, N->Y, N->P, I->N, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "09461851", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from I to N.", "answer": "['I->N', 'I->H->N', 'I->P<-N']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, H, N, T, P, Y and directed edges H->N, I->H, I->P, N->Y, N->P, I->N, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "09461851", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from N to T.", "answer": "1", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, H, N, T, P, Y and directed edges H->N, I->H, I->P, N->Y, N->P, I->N, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "09461851", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from H to T.", "answer": ["H->N->T", "H<-I->N->T", "H<-I->P<-N->T"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, H, N, T, P, Y and directed edges H->N, I->H, I->P, N->Y, N->P, I->N, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "09461851", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from H to T.", "answer": "H->N->T", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, H, N, T, P, Y and directed edges H->N, I->H, I->P, N->Y, N->P, I->N, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "09461851", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from H to T.", "answer": "H<-I->P<-N->T", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, H, N, T, P, Y and directed edges H->N, I->H, I->P, N->Y, N->P, I->N, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "09461851", "sid": 5, "question": "Is N->T a path from N to T?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, H, N, T, P, Y and directed edges H->N, I->H, I->P, N->Y, N->P, I->N, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "09461851", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from Y to H?\nA. Y<-N->P<-I->H\nB. Y<->N<->H\nC. Y->T->N<->H\nD. Y<-N->H", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes D, R, Q, W, O, I, G and directed edges Q->O, O->G, W->I, D->R, Q->W, W->G, R->O, R->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "38464784", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from D to I.", "answer": "['D->R->I', 'D->R->O<-Q->W->I', 'D->R->O->G<-W->I']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes D, R, Q, W, O, I, G and directed edges Q->O, O->G, W->I, D->R, Q->W, W->G, R->O, R->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "38464784", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from Q to D.", "answer": "4", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes D, R, Q, W, O, I, G and directed edges Q->O, O->G, W->I, D->R, Q->W, W->G, R->O, R->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "38464784", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from Q to I.", "answer": ["Q->W->I", "Q->O<-R->I", "Q->O->G<-W->I", "Q->W->G<-O<-R->I"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes D, R, Q, W, O, I, G and directed edges Q->O, O->G, W->I, D->R, Q->W, W->G, R->O, R->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "38464784", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from Q to I.", "answer": "Q->W->I", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes D, R, Q, W, O, I, G and directed edges Q->O, O->G, W->I, D->R, Q->W, W->G, R->O, R->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "38464784", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from Q to I.", "answer": "Q->W->G<-O<-R->I", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes D, R, Q, W, O, I, G and directed edges Q->O, O->G, W->I, D->R, Q->W, W->G, R->O, R->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "38464784", "sid": 5, "question": "Is O->G<-W->I<-R a path from O to R?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes D, R, Q, W, O, I, G and directed edges Q->O, O->G, W->I, D->R, Q->W, W->G, R->O, R->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "38464784", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from R to G?\nA. R<->D<-O->G\nB. R->I<-W<-Q->O->G\nC. R<-I<-Q<-O<-G\nD. R->I<-G", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, Z, I, W, T, P, J and directed edges E->Z, E->P, T->J, E->I, E->J, P->J, I->P, E->T, Z->W.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "07330327", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from Z to J.", "answer": "['Z<-E->J', 'Z<-E->P->J', 'Z<-E->T->J', 'Z<-E->I->P->J']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, Z, I, W, T, P, J and directed edges E->Z, E->P, T->J, E->I, E->J, P->J, I->P, E->T, Z->W.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "07330327", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from J to P.", "answer": "5", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, Z, I, W, T, P, J and directed edges E->Z, E->P, T->J, E->I, E->J, P->J, I->P, E->T, Z->W.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "07330327", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from P to I.", "answer": ["P<-I", "P<-E->I", "P->J<-E->I", "P->J<-T<-E->I"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, Z, I, W, T, P, J and directed edges E->Z, E->P, T->J, E->I, E->J, P->J, I->P, E->T, Z->W.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "07330327", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from P to I.", "answer": "P<-I", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, Z, I, W, T, P, J and directed edges E->Z, E->P, T->J, E->I, E->J, P->J, I->P, E->T, Z->W.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "07330327", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from P to I.", "answer": "P->J<-T<-E->I", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, Z, I, W, T, P, J and directed edges E->Z, E->P, T->J, E->I, E->J, P->J, I->P, E->T, Z->W.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "07330327", "sid": 5, "question": "Is I<-E->Z a path from I to Z?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, Z, I, W, T, P, J and directed edges E->Z, E->P, T->J, E->I, E->J, P->J, I->P, E->T, Z->W.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "07330327", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from I to E?\nA. I<-T<-E\nB. I->P->J<-T<-E\nC. I<->W->E\nD. I<-Z->E", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes S, D, X, F, N, R, Y, I and directed edges D->N, X->F, N->Y, F->I, D->F, D->R, F->R, F->N, S->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "66990225", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from D to F.", "answer": "['D->F', 'D->N<-F', 'D->R<-F']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes S, D, X, F, N, R, Y, I and directed edges D->N, X->F, N->Y, F->I, D->F, D->R, F->R, F->N, S->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "66990225", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from Y to S.", "answer": "3", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes S, D, X, F, N, R, Y, I and directed edges D->N, X->F, N->Y, F->I, D->F, D->R, F->R, F->N, S->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "66990225", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from D to R.", "answer": ["D->R", "D->F->R", "D->N<-F->R"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes S, D, X, F, N, R, Y, I and directed edges D->N, X->F, N->Y, F->I, D->F, D->R, F->R, F->N, S->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "66990225", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from D to R.", "answer": "D->R", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes S, D, X, F, N, R, Y, I and directed edges D->N, X->F, N->Y, F->I, D->F, D->R, F->R, F->N, S->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "66990225", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from D to R.", "answer": "D->N<-F->R", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes S, D, X, F, N, R, Y, I and directed edges D->N, X->F, N->Y, F->I, D->F, D->R, F->R, F->N, S->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "66990225", "sid": 5, "question": "Is Y<-N<-F->I a path from Y to I?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes S, D, X, F, N, R, Y, I and directed edges D->N, X->F, N->Y, F->I, D->F, D->R, F->R, F->N, S->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "66990225", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from F to N?\nA. F<-S<->X<->N\nB. F->Y<-N\nC. F->R<-D->N\nD. F->I<-R<->D<->N", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, T, V, M, X, N, E, P and directed edges T->P, N->E, G->V, X->E, G->T, G->P, V->N, M->P, M->N.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "97481750", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from N to P.", "answer": "['N<-M->P', 'N<-V<-G->P', 'N<-V<-G->T->P']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, T, V, M, X, N, E, P and directed edges T->P, N->E, G->V, X->E, G->T, G->P, V->N, M->P, M->N.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "97481750", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from N to P.", "answer": "3", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, T, V, M, X, N, E, P and directed edges T->P, N->E, G->V, X->E, G->T, G->P, V->N, M->P, M->N.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "97481750", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from G to E.", "answer": ["G->V->N->E", "G->P<-M->N->E", "G->T->P<-M->N->E"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, T, V, M, X, N, E, P and directed edges T->P, N->E, G->V, X->E, G->T, G->P, V->N, M->P, M->N.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "97481750", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from G to E.", "answer": "G->V->N->E", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, T, V, M, X, N, E, P and directed edges T->P, N->E, G->V, X->E, G->T, G->P, V->N, M->P, M->N.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "97481750", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from G to E.", "answer": "G->T->P<-M->N->E", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, T, V, M, X, N, E, P and directed edges T->P, N->E, G->V, X->E, G->T, G->P, V->N, M->P, M->N.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "97481750", "sid": 5, "question": "Is M->V->G a path from M to G?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, T, V, M, X, N, E, P and directed edges T->P, N->E, G->V, X->E, G->T, G->P, V->N, M->P, M->N.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "97481750", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from X to G?\nA. X->E<-N<-M->P<-T<-G\nB. X<->P<->M->G\nC. X<-V->T->G\nD. X<->P<->M<-G", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, B, I, M, A, K, Z, C, Y and directed edges B->C, A->K, B->I, B->Y, K->Y, B->K, I->Z, K->C, M->A, H->Y, M->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22897623", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from Y to Z.", "answer": "['Y<-B->I->Z', 'Y<-K<-B->I->Z', 'Y<-K->C<-B->I->Z', 'Y<-M->A->K<-B->I->Z', 'Y<-M->A->K->C<-B->I->Z']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, B, I, M, A, K, Z, C, Y and directed edges B->C, A->K, B->I, B->Y, K->Y, B->K, I->Z, K->C, M->A, H->Y, M->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22897623", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from I to A.", "answer": "6", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, B, I, M, A, K, Z, C, Y and directed edges B->C, A->K, B->I, B->Y, K->Y, B->K, I->Z, K->C, M->A, H->Y, M->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22897623", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from B to Z.", "answer": ["B->I->Z"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, B, I, M, A, K, Z, C, Y and directed edges B->C, A->K, B->I, B->Y, K->Y, B->K, I->Z, K->C, M->A, H->Y, M->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22897623", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from B to Z.", "answer": "B->I->Z", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, B, I, M, A, K, Z, C, Y and directed edges B->C, A->K, B->I, B->Y, K->Y, B->K, I->Z, K->C, M->A, H->Y, M->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22897623", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from B to Z.", "answer": "B->I->Z", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, B, I, M, A, K, Z, C, Y and directed edges B->C, A->K, B->I, B->Y, K->Y, B->K, I->Z, K->C, M->A, H->Y, M->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22897623", "sid": 5, "question": "Is K<->H<->A<-I a path from K to I?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, B, I, M, A, K, Z, C, Y and directed edges B->C, A->K, B->I, B->Y, K->Y, B->K, I->Z, K->C, M->A, H->Y, M->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22897623", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from M to A?\nA. M->Y<-B->C<-K<-A\nB. M<-K<->A\nC. M<->I<-A\nD. M->K<-I->A", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes R, T, L, K, Z, S, F, V, I and directed edges T->F, T->L, L->V, Z->S, Z->I, T->K, S->V, R->Z, S->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40102907", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from S to Z.", "answer": "['S<-Z', 'S->I<-Z']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes R, T, L, K, Z, S, F, V, I and directed edges T->F, T->L, L->V, Z->S, Z->I, T->K, S->V, R->Z, S->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40102907", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from I to F.", "answer": "2", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes R, T, L, K, Z, S, F, V, I and directed edges T->F, T->L, L->V, Z->S, Z->I, T->K, S->V, R->Z, S->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40102907", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from F to I.", "answer": ["F<-T->L->V<-S->I", "F<-T->L->V<-S<-Z->I"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes R, T, L, K, Z, S, F, V, I and directed edges T->F, T->L, L->V, Z->S, Z->I, T->K, S->V, R->Z, S->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40102907", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from F to I.", "answer": "F<-T->L->V<-S->I", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes R, T, L, K, Z, S, F, V, I and directed edges T->F, T->L, L->V, Z->S, Z->I, T->K, S->V, R->Z, S->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40102907", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from F to I.", "answer": "F<-T->L->V<-S<-Z->I", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes R, T, L, K, Z, S, F, V, I and directed edges T->F, T->L, L->V, Z->S, Z->I, T->K, S->V, R->Z, S->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40102907", "sid": 5, "question": "Is T->L->V<-S<-Z->I a path from T to I?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes R, T, L, K, Z, S, F, V, I and directed edges T->F, T->L, L->V, Z->S, Z->I, T->K, S->V, R->Z, S->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40102907", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from V to S?\nA. V<->L<-K->S\nB. V->F<->S\nC. V<->I<->T->S\nD. V<-S", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, B, R, E, directed edges K->R, B->R, K->E, K->B and bi-directed edges B<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "20569823", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from B to E.", "answer": "['B<->E', 'B<-K->E', 'B->R<-K->E']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, B, R, E, directed edges K->R, B->R, K->E, K->B and bi-directed edges B<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "20569823", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from B to K.", "answer": "3", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, B, R, E, directed edges K->R, B->R, K->E, K->B and bi-directed edges B<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "20569823", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from B to E.", "answer": ["B<->E", "B<-K->E", "B->R<-K->E"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, B, R, E, directed edges K->R, B->R, K->E, K->B and bi-directed edges B<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "20569823", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from B to E.", "answer": "B<->E", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, B, R, E, directed edges K->R, B->R, K->E, K->B and bi-directed edges B<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "20569823", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from B to E.", "answer": "B->R<-K->E", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, B, R, E, directed edges K->R, B->R, K->E, K->B and bi-directed edges B<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "20569823", "sid": 5, "question": "Is R<->E<-K a path from R to K?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, B, R, E, directed edges K->R, B->R, K->E, K->B and bi-directed edges B<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "20569823", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from R to K?\nA. R<->B->E<-K\nB. R->E<->B<-K\nC. R<-B<-K\nD. R->B->K", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Z, D, M, G, directed edges D->G, D->M, M->G, Z->D, Z->G, Z->M and bi-directed edges M<->G, Z<->M, Z<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48119117", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from D to Z.", "answer": "['D<-Z', 'D<->Z', 'D->G<-Z', 'D->M<-Z', 'D->M<->Z', 'D->G<-M<-Z', 'D->G<-M<->Z', 'D->G<->M<-Z', 'D->G<->M<->Z', 'D->M->G<-Z', 'D->M<->G<-Z']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Z, D, M, G, directed edges D->G, D->M, M->G, Z->D, Z->G, Z->M and bi-directed edges M<->G, Z<->M, Z<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48119117", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from M to Z.", "answer": "11", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Z, D, M, G, directed edges D->G, D->M, M->G, Z->D, Z->G, Z->M and bi-directed edges M<->G, Z<->M, Z<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48119117", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from Z to M.", "answer": ["Z->M", "Z<->M", "Z->G<-M", "Z->G<->M", "Z->D->M", "Z<->D->M", "Z->G<-D->M", "Z->D->G<-M", "Z->D->G<->M", "Z<->D->G<-M", "Z<->D->G<->M"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Z, D, M, G, directed edges D->G, D->M, M->G, Z->D, Z->G, Z->M and bi-directed edges M<->G, Z<->M, Z<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48119117", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from Z to M.", "answer": "Z->M", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Z, D, M, G, directed edges D->G, D->M, M->G, Z->D, Z->G, Z->M and bi-directed edges M<->G, Z<->M, Z<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48119117", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from Z to M.", "answer": "Z<->D->G<->M", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Z, D, M, G, directed edges D->G, D->M, M->G, Z->D, Z->G, Z->M and bi-directed edges M<->G, Z<->M, Z<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48119117", "sid": 5, "question": "Is G<-D->Z a path from G to Z?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Z, D, M, G, directed edges D->G, D->M, M->G, Z->D, Z->G, Z->M and bi-directed edges M<->G, Z<->M, Z<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48119117", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from Z to M?\nA. Z<->G<->D<-M\nB. Z<->G<-M\nC. Z->D->G<-M\nD. Z<-D<->G<-M", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes I, N, W, E, B, directed edges N->B, W->E, I->N, I->E, N->W, W->B, N->E, I->B and bi-directed edges I<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "60155994", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from B to N.", "answer": "['B<-N', 'B<-I->N', 'B<-W<-N', 'B<-I->E<-N', 'B<-I<->E<-N', 'B<-W->E<-N', 'B<-I->E<-W<-N', 'B<-I<->E<-W<-N', 'B<-W->E<-I->N', 'B<-W->E<->I->N']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes I, N, W, E, B, directed edges N->B, W->E, I->N, I->E, N->W, W->B, N->E, I->B and bi-directed edges I<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "60155994", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from I to B.", "answer": "12", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes I, N, W, E, B, directed edges N->B, W->E, I->N, I->E, N->W, W->B, N->E, I->B and bi-directed edges I<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "60155994", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from N to B.", "answer": ["N->B", "N<-I->B", "N->W->B", "N->E<-I->B", "N->E<->I->B", "N->E<-W->B", "N<-I->E<-W->B", "N<-I<->E<-W->B", "N->W->E<-I->B", "N->W->E<->I->B"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes I, N, W, E, B, directed edges N->B, W->E, I->N, I->E, N->W, W->B, N->E, I->B and bi-directed edges I<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "60155994", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from N to B.", "answer": "N->B", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes I, N, W, E, B, directed edges N->B, W->E, I->N, I->E, N->W, W->B, N->E, I->B and bi-directed edges I<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "60155994", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from N to B.", "answer": "N<-I<->E<-W->B", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes I, N, W, E, B, directed edges N->B, W->E, I->N, I->E, N->W, W->B, N->E, I->B and bi-directed edges I<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "60155994", "sid": 5, "question": "Is E<-I->N->B<-W a path from E to W?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes I, N, W, E, B, directed edges N->B, W->E, I->N, I->E, N->W, W->B, N->E, I->B and bi-directed edges I<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "60155994", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from W to E?\nA. W->N<-B->I<-E\nB. W->B<-I->N->E\nC. W->I->E\nD. W<-I->N<-E", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, Q, I, L, D, directed edges Q->I, K->D, I->L, Q->D, K->L, Q->L, I->D and bi-directed edges I<->L, Q<->I, K<->Q.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "57939882", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from I to Q.", "answer": "['I<-Q', 'I<->Q', 'I->L<-Q', 'I<->L<-Q', 'I->D<-Q', 'I->L<-K<->Q', 'I<->L<-K<->Q', 'I->D<-K<->Q', 'I->L<-K->D<-Q', 'I<->L<-K->D<-Q', 'I->D<-K->L<-Q']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, Q, I, L, D, directed edges Q->I, K->D, I->L, Q->D, K->L, Q->L, I->D and bi-directed edges I<->L, Q<->I, K<->Q.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "57939882", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from I to L.", "answer": "12", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, Q, I, L, D, directed edges Q->I, K->D, I->L, Q->D, K->L, Q->L, I->D and bi-directed edges I<->L, Q<->I, K<->Q.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "57939882", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from D to L.", "answer": ["D<-Q->L", "D<-I->L", "D<-I<->L", "D<-K->L", "D<-Q->I->L", "D<-Q->I<->L", "D<-Q<->I->L", "D<-Q<->I<->L", "D<-Q<->K->L", "D<-I<-Q->L", "D<-I<->Q->L", "D<-K<->Q->L", "D<-I<-Q<->K->L", "D<-I<->Q<->K->L", "D<-K<->Q->I->L", "D<-K<->Q->I<->L", "D<-K<->Q<->I->L", "D<-K<->Q<->I<->L"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, Q, I, L, D, directed edges Q->I, K->D, I->L, Q->D, K->L, Q->L, I->D and bi-directed edges I<->L, Q<->I, K<->Q.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "57939882", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from D to L.", "answer": "D<-Q->L", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, Q, I, L, D, directed edges Q->I, K->D, I->L, Q->D, K->L, Q->L, I->D and bi-directed edges I<->L, Q<->I, K<->Q.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "57939882", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from D to L.", "answer": "D<-K<->Q<->I<->L", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, Q, I, L, D, directed edges Q->I, K->D, I->L, Q->D, K->L, Q->L, I->D and bi-directed edges I<->L, Q<->I, K<->Q.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "57939882", "sid": 5, "question": "Is I<-Q<-L<->D a path from I to D?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, Q, I, L, D, directed edges Q->I, K->D, I->L, Q->D, K->L, Q->L, I->D and bi-directed edges I<->L, Q<->I, K<->Q.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "57939882", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from I to K?\nA. I<->D<-K\nB. I->D<-Q<->K\nC. I<->D<->K\nD. I<-L<->Q->D<->K", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, H, I, D, N, G, directed edges H->D, D->N, Q->D, I->N, Q->G, Q->H and bi-directed edges H<->I, D<->G.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44298261", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from D to G.", "answer": "['D<->G', 'D<-Q->G', 'D<-H<-Q->G', 'D->N<-I<->H<-Q->G']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, H, I, D, N, G, directed edges H->D, D->N, Q->D, I->N, Q->G, Q->H and bi-directed edges H<->I, D<->G.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44298261", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from I to Q.", "answer": "6", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, H, I, D, N, G, directed edges H->D, D->N, Q->D, I->N, Q->G, Q->H and bi-directed edges H<->I, D<->G.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44298261", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from I to N.", "answer": ["I->N", "I<->H->D->N", "I<->H<-Q->D->N", "I<->H<-Q->G<->D->N"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, H, I, D, N, G, directed edges H->D, D->N, Q->D, I->N, Q->G, Q->H and bi-directed edges H<->I, D<->G.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44298261", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from I to N.", "answer": "I->N", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, H, I, D, N, G, directed edges H->D, D->N, Q->D, I->N, Q->G, Q->H and bi-directed edges H<->I, D<->G.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44298261", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from I to N.", "answer": "I<->H<-Q->G<->D->N", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, H, I, D, N, G, directed edges H->D, D->N, Q->D, I->N, Q->G, Q->H and bi-directed edges H<->I, D<->G.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44298261", "sid": 5, "question": "Is N<-I a path from N to I?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, H, I, D, N, G, directed edges H->D, D->N, Q->D, I->N, Q->G, Q->H and bi-directed edges H<->I, D<->G.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44298261", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from N to D?\nA. N<-Q<->I<->H<-D\nB. N->Q->G<->I<->D\nC. N<-I<->H<-Q->D\nD. N<-Q<-D", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes S, U, O, D, N, V, directed edges S->D, S->V, N->V, S->O, U->N, S->N, D->V, U->O, D->N and bi-directed edges O<->V, N<->V.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "61577952", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from V to D.", "answer": "['V<-D', 'V<-S->D', 'V<-N<-D', 'V<->N<-D', 'V<->O<-S->D', 'V<-S->N<-D', 'V<-N<-S->D', 'V<->N<-S->D', 'V<->O<-S->N<-D', 'V<->O<-U->N<-D', 'V<->O<-U->N<-S->D', 'V<-S->O<-U->N<-D', 'V<-N<-U->O<-S->D', 'V<->N<-U->O<-S->D']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes S, U, O, D, N, V, directed edges S->D, S->V, N->V, S->O, U->N, S->N, D->V, U->O, D->N and bi-directed edges O<->V, N<->V.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "61577952", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from D to S.", "answer": "15", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes S, U, O, D, N, V, directed edges S->D, S->V, N->V, S->O, U->N, S->N, D->V, U->O, D->N and bi-directed edges O<->V, N<->V.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "61577952", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from D to S.", "answer": ["D<-S", "D->V<-S", "D->N<-S", "D->V<->O<-S", "D->V<-N<-S", "D->V<->N<-S", "D->N->V<-S", "D->N<->V<-S", "D->N<-U->O<-S", "D->N->V<->O<-S", "D->N<->V<->O<-S", "D->V<->O<-U->N<-S", "D->V<-N<-U->O<-S", "D->V<->N<-U->O<-S", "D->N<-U->O<->V<-S"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes S, U, O, D, N, V, directed edges S->D, S->V, N->V, S->O, U->N, S->N, D->V, U->O, D->N and bi-directed edges O<->V, N<->V.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "61577952", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from D to S.", "answer": "D<-S", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes S, U, O, D, N, V, directed edges S->D, S->V, N->V, S->O, U->N, S->N, D->V, U->O, D->N and bi-directed edges O<->V, N<->V.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "61577952", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from D to S.", "answer": "D->V<->O<-U->N<-S", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes S, U, O, D, N, V, directed edges S->D, S->V, N->V, S->O, U->N, S->N, D->V, U->O, D->N and bi-directed edges O<->V, N<->V.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "61577952", "sid": 5, "question": "Is D<-S->V a path from D to V?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes S, U, O, D, N, V, directed edges S->D, S->V, N->V, S->O, U->N, S->N, D->V, U->O, D->N and bi-directed edges O<->V, N<->V.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "61577952", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from O to V?\nA. O<-U<->D<-V\nB. O<-U->N->V\nC. O<-D->U<->S<->V\nD. O<->S<->V", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes P, N, Z, T, H, K, S, directed edges N->K, Z->T, H->K, H->S, N->H, P->Z, Z->K and bi-directed edges T<->K, N<->K, N<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "71424828", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from K to S.", "answer": "['K<-H->S', 'K<-N->H->S', 'K<->N->H->S', 'K<->T<->N->H->S', 'K<-Z->T<->N->H->S']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes P, N, Z, T, H, K, S, directed edges N->K, Z->T, H->K, H->S, N->H, P->Z, Z->K and bi-directed edges T<->K, N<->K, N<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "71424828", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from T to P.", "answer": "5", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes P, N, Z, T, H, K, S, directed edges N->K, Z->T, H->K, H->S, N->H, P->Z, Z->K and bi-directed edges T<->K, N<->K, N<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "71424828", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from N to K.", "answer": ["N->K", "N<->K", "N->H->K", "N<->T<->K", "N<->T<-Z->K"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes P, N, Z, T, H, K, S, directed edges N->K, Z->T, H->K, H->S, N->H, P->Z, Z->K and bi-directed edges T<->K, N<->K, N<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "71424828", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from N to K.", "answer": "N->K", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes P, N, Z, T, H, K, S, directed edges N->K, Z->T, H->K, H->S, N->H, P->Z, Z->K and bi-directed edges T<->K, N<->K, N<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "71424828", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from N to K.", "answer": "N<->T<-Z->K", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes P, N, Z, T, H, K, S, directed edges N->K, Z->T, H->K, H->S, N->H, P->Z, Z->K and bi-directed edges T<->K, N<->K, N<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "71424828", "sid": 5, "question": "Is N->H->T a path from N to T?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes P, N, Z, T, H, K, S, directed edges N->K, Z->T, H->K, H->S, N->H, P->Z, Z->K and bi-directed edges T<->K, N<->K, N<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "71424828", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from N to P?\nA. N<-K->T<->P\nB. N->Z<->S->T->P\nC. N<-S<->T<->Z->P\nD. N->K<->T<-Z<-P", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Z, F, V, O, Y, W, U, directed edges Y->U, V->W, Y->W, O->Y, Z->V, V->U, V->Y, V->O, F->Y, W->U and bi-directed edges O<->Y, V<->Y, V<->O, F<->W, V<->W.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "88111889", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from W to O.", "answer": "['W<-Y<-O', 'W<-Y<->O', 'W<-V->O', 'W<-V<->O', 'W<->V->O', 'W<->V<->O', 'W<-Y<-V->O', 'W<-Y<-V<->O', 'W<-Y<->V->O', 'W<-Y<->V<->O', 'W->U<-Y<-O', 'W->U<-Y<->O', 'W->U<-V->O', 'W->U<-V<->O', 'W<-V->Y<-O', 'W<-V->Y<->O', 'W<-V<->Y<-O', 'W<-V<->Y<->O', 'W<->V->Y<-O', 'W<->V->Y<->O', 'W<->V<->Y<-O', 'W<->V<->Y<->O', 'W<->F->Y<-O', 'W<->F->Y<->O', 'W<-Y->U<-V->O', 'W<-Y->U<-V<->O', 'W->U<-Y<-V->O', 'W->U<-Y<-V<->O', 'W->U<-Y<->V->O', 'W->U<-Y<->V<->O', 'W->U<-V->Y<-O', 'W->U<-V->Y<->O', 'W->U<-V<->Y<-O', 'W->U<-V<->Y<->O', 'W<-V->U<-Y<-O', 'W<-V->U<-Y<->O', 'W<->V->U<-Y<-O', 'W<->V->U<-Y<->O', 'W<->F->Y<-V->O', 'W<->F->Y<-V<->O', 'W<->F->Y<->V->O', 'W<->F->Y<->V<->O', 'W<->F->Y->U<-V->O', 'W<->F->Y->U<-V<->O']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Z, F, V, O, Y, W, U, directed edges Y->U, V->W, Y->W, O->Y, Z->V, V->U, V->Y, V->O, F->Y, W->U and bi-directed edges O<->Y, V<->Y, V<->O, F<->W, V<->W.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "88111889", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from Y to W.", "answer": "23", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Z, F, V, O, Y, W, U, directed edges Y->U, V->W, Y->W, O->Y, Z->V, V->U, V->Y, V->O, F->Y, W->U and bi-directed edges O<->Y, V<->Y, V<->O, F<->W, V<->W.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "88111889", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from Z to V.", "answer": ["Z->V"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Z, F, V, O, Y, W, U, directed edges Y->U, V->W, Y->W, O->Y, Z->V, V->U, V->Y, V->O, F->Y, W->U and bi-directed edges O<->Y, V<->Y, V<->O, F<->W, V<->W.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "88111889", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from Z to V.", "answer": "Z->V", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Z, F, V, O, Y, W, U, directed edges Y->U, V->W, Y->W, O->Y, Z->V, V->U, V->Y, V->O, F->Y, W->U and bi-directed edges O<->Y, V<->Y, V<->O, F<->W, V<->W.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "88111889", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from Z to V.", "answer": "Z->V", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Z, F, V, O, Y, W, U, directed edges Y->U, V->W, Y->W, O->Y, Z->V, V->U, V->Y, V->O, F->Y, W->U and bi-directed edges O<->Y, V<->Y, V<->O, F<->W, V<->W.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "88111889", "sid": 5, "question": "Is Y<->V<->W<->F a path from Y to F?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Z, F, V, O, Y, W, U, directed edges Y->U, V->W, Y->W, O->Y, Z->V, V->U, V->Y, V->O, F->Y, W->U and bi-directed edges O<->Y, V<->Y, V<->O, F<->W, V<->W.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "88111889", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from U to Z?\nA. U<->Y<->F->Z\nB. U->F<->W<->O->Z\nC. U<-W<-Y<->O<->V<-Z\nD. U->Y<-O->W->Z", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes E, R, Q, V, S, U, K, T, directed edges E->V, Q->U, S->U, Q->V, R->K, E->K, S->T, V->S, E->U and bi-directed edges R<->S, Q<->K, S<->K, Q<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "90406830", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from E to S.", "answer": "['E->V->S', 'E->U<-S', 'E->K<->S', 'E->K<-R<->S', 'E->V<-Q->U<-S', 'E->V<-Q<->K<->S', 'E->V<-Q<->T<-S', 'E->U<-Q<->K<->S', 'E->U<-Q->V->S', 'E->U<-Q<->T<-S', 'E->K<->Q->U<-S', 'E->K<->Q->V->S', 'E->K<->Q<->T<-S', 'E->V<-Q<->K<-R<->S', 'E->U<-Q<->K<-R<->S']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes E, R, Q, V, S, U, K, T, directed edges E->V, Q->U, S->U, Q->V, R->K, E->K, S->T, V->S, E->U and bi-directed edges R<->S, Q<->K, S<->K, Q<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "90406830", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from T to Q.", "answer": "13", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes E, R, Q, V, S, U, K, T, directed edges E->V, Q->U, S->U, Q->V, R->K, E->K, S->T, V->S, E->U and bi-directed edges R<->S, Q<->K, S<->K, Q<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "90406830", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from K to S.", "answer": ["K<->S", "K<-R<->S", "K<->Q->U<-S", "K<->Q->V->S", "K<->Q<->T<-S", "K<-E->V->S", "K<-E->U<-S", "K<->Q->U<-E->V->S", "K<->Q->V<-E->U<-S", "K<-E->V<-Q->U<-S", "K<-E->V<-Q<->T<-S", "K<-E->U<-Q->V->S", "K<-E->U<-Q<->T<-S"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes E, R, Q, V, S, U, K, T, directed edges E->V, Q->U, S->U, Q->V, R->K, E->K, S->T, V->S, E->U and bi-directed edges R<->S, Q<->K, S<->K, Q<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "90406830", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from K to S.", "answer": "K<->S", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes E, R, Q, V, S, U, K, T, directed edges E->V, Q->U, S->U, Q->V, R->K, E->K, S->T, V->S, E->U and bi-directed edges R<->S, Q<->K, S<->K, Q<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "90406830", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from K to S.", "answer": "K<->Q->U<-E->V->S", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes E, R, Q, V, S, U, K, T, directed edges E->V, Q->U, S->U, Q->V, R->K, E->K, S->T, V->S, E->U and bi-directed edges R<->S, Q<->K, S<->K, Q<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "90406830", "sid": 5, "question": "Is V<-Q->U<-E->K<->S a path from V to S?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes E, R, Q, V, S, U, K, T, directed edges E->V, Q->U, S->U, Q->V, R->K, E->K, S->T, V->S, E->U and bi-directed edges R<->S, Q<->K, S<->K, Q<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "90406830", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from U to S?\nA. U<-E<-K<->S\nB. U<-V<->K->S\nC. U<-E->K<->Q<->T<-S\nD. U->T<-R<->K->S", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, F, Q, W, S, M, A, C, directed edges F->C, Q->W, Y->F, Y->M, S->A, Q->S, Y->W, Y->C, W->C, M->C and bi-directed edges W<->S.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48562725", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from W to S.", "answer": "['W<->S', 'W<-Q->S']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, F, Q, W, S, M, A, C, directed edges F->C, Q->W, Y->F, Y->M, S->A, Q->S, Y->W, Y->C, W->C, M->C and bi-directed edges W<->S.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48562725", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from Y to F.", "answer": "4", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, F, Q, W, S, M, A, C, directed edges F->C, Q->W, Y->F, Y->M, S->A, Q->S, Y->W, Y->C, W->C, M->C and bi-directed edges W<->S.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48562725", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from F to C.", "answer": ["F->C", "F<-Y->C", "F<-Y->M->C", "F<-Y->W->C"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, F, Q, W, S, M, A, C, directed edges F->C, Q->W, Y->F, Y->M, S->A, Q->S, Y->W, Y->C, W->C, M->C and bi-directed edges W<->S.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48562725", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from F to C.", "answer": "F->C", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, F, Q, W, S, M, A, C, directed edges F->C, Q->W, Y->F, Y->M, S->A, Q->S, Y->W, Y->C, W->C, M->C and bi-directed edges W<->S.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48562725", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from F to C.", "answer": "F<-Y->M->C", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, F, Q, W, S, M, A, C, directed edges F->C, Q->W, Y->F, Y->M, S->A, Q->S, Y->W, Y->C, W->C, M->C and bi-directed edges W<->S.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48562725", "sid": 5, "question": "Is F->C a path from F to C?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, F, Q, W, S, M, A, C, directed edges F->C, Q->W, Y->F, Y->M, S->A, Q->S, Y->W, Y->C, W->C, M->C and bi-directed edges W<->S.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48562725", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from M to C?\nA. M<-F<-Q<-C\nB. M->C\nC. M<-F<-Y<-S->C\nD. M<->A<->Y<->W->C", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes L, Z, A, C, O, E, K, Q, X, directed edges O->X, Z->A, A->K, L->E, Q->X, O->K, A->C, L->Q, L->K and bi-directed edges O<->Q, A<->C, L<->X, C<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "32213785", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from Z to K.", "answer": "['Z->A->K', 'Z->A->C<->E<-L->K', 'Z->A<->C<->E<-L->K', 'Z->A->C<->E<-L->Q<->O->K', 'Z->A->C<->E<-L<->X<-O->K', 'Z->A<->C<->E<-L->Q<->O->K', 'Z->A<->C<->E<-L<->X<-O->K', 'Z->A->C<->E<-L->Q->X<-O->K', 'Z->A->C<->E<-L<->X<-Q<->O->K', 'Z->A<->C<->E<-L->Q->X<-O->K', 'Z->A<->C<->E<-L<->X<-Q<->O->K']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes L, Z, A, C, O, E, K, Q, X, directed edges O->X, Z->A, A->K, L->E, Q->X, O->K, A->C, L->Q, L->K and bi-directed edges O<->Q, A<->C, L<->X, C<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "32213785", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from C to E.", "answer": "11", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes L, Z, A, C, O, E, K, Q, X, directed edges O->X, Z->A, A->K, L->E, Q->X, O->K, A->C, L->Q, L->K and bi-directed edges O<->Q, A<->C, L<->X, C<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "32213785", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from C to L.", "answer": ["C<->E<-L", "C<-A->K<-L", "C<->A->K<-L", "C<-A->K<-O<->Q<-L", "C<-A->K<-O->X<->L", "C<->A->K<-O<->Q<-L", "C<->A->K<-O->X<->L", "C<-A->K<-O<->Q->X<->L", "C<-A->K<-O->X<-Q<-L", "C<->A->K<-O<->Q->X<->L", "C<->A->K<-O->X<-Q<-L"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes L, Z, A, C, O, E, K, Q, X, directed edges O->X, Z->A, A->K, L->E, Q->X, O->K, A->C, L->Q, L->K and bi-directed edges O<->Q, A<->C, L<->X, C<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "32213785", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from C to L.", "answer": "C<->E<-L", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes L, Z, A, C, O, E, K, Q, X, directed edges O->X, Z->A, A->K, L->E, Q->X, O->K, A->C, L->Q, L->K and bi-directed edges O<->Q, A<->C, L<->X, C<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "32213785", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from C to L.", "answer": "C<->A->K<-O<->Q->X<->L", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes L, Z, A, C, O, E, K, Q, X, directed edges O->X, Z->A, A->K, L->E, Q->X, O->K, A->C, L->Q, L->K and bi-directed edges O<->Q, A<->C, L<->X, C<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "32213785", "sid": 5, "question": "Is O->K<-A<->C<->E a path from O to E?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes L, Z, A, C, O, E, K, Q, X, directed edges O->X, Z->A, A->K, L->E, Q->X, O->K, A->C, L->Q, L->K and bi-directed edges O<->Q, A<->C, L<->X, C<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "32213785", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from A to O?\nA. A->C<->E<-L<->X<-O\nB. A<->C->K<->Z<-O\nC. A->Z<->O\nD. A->C->Z<-O", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, Z, M, G, U, P, A, W, T, directed edges Z->W, G->T, Y->Z, U->T, A->W, Y->T, P->W, G->W, M->T and bi-directed edges G<->U, Z<->W, Y<->Z.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "86722896", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all paths from P to A.", "answer": "['P->W<-A']", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, Z, M, G, U, P, A, W, T, directed edges Z->W, G->T, Y->Z, U->T, A->W, Y->T, P->W, G->W, M->T and bi-directed edges G<->U, Z<->W, Y<->Z.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "86722896", "sid": 1, "question": "How many paths are there from M to W.", "answer": "6", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, Z, M, G, U, P, A, W, T, directed edges Z->W, G->T, Y->Z, U->T, A->W, Y->T, P->W, G->W, M->T and bi-directed edges G<->U, Z<->W, Y<->Z.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "86722896", "sid": 2, "question": "Find one path from Z to U.", "answer": ["Z<-Y->T<-U", "Z<->Y->T<-U", "Z->W<-G<->U", "Z<->W<-G<->U", "Z<-Y->T<-G<->U", "Z<->Y->T<-G<->U", "Z->W<-G->T<-U", "Z<->W<-G->T<-U"], "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, Z, M, G, U, P, A, W, T, directed edges Z->W, G->T, Y->Z, U->T, A->W, Y->T, P->W, G->W, M->T and bi-directed edges G<->U, Z<->W, Y<->Z.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "86722896", "sid": 3, "question": "Find the shortest paths from Z to U.", "answer": "Z<-Y->T<-U", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, Z, M, G, U, P, A, W, T, directed edges Z->W, G->T, Y->Z, U->T, A->W, Y->T, P->W, G->W, M->T and bi-directed edges G<->U, Z<->W, Y<->Z.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "86722896", "sid": 4, "question": "Find the longest paths from Z to U.", "answer": "Z<->Y->T<-G<->U", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, Z, M, G, U, P, A, W, T, directed edges Z->W, G->T, Y->Z, U->T, A->W, Y->T, P->W, G->W, M->T and bi-directed edges G<->U, Z<->W, Y<->Z.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "86722896", "sid": 5, "question": "Is U<->W->Z->T<->P a path from U to P?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, Z, M, G, U, P, A, W, T, directed edges Z->W, G->T, Y->Z, U->T, A->W, Y->T, P->W, G->W, M->T and bi-directed edges G<->U, Z<->W, Y<->Z.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "86722896", "sid": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a path from Y to G?\nA. Y->Z<->W<-G\nB. Y->M->W<-P->G\nC. Y<-P<->Z<->M->G\nD. Y<-M->G", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "path"}
